Here's something that's odd to me.
A lot of y'all know these three very empirical truths.
One, this globe is run by colonialism and imperialism.
Two, the media is run by white supremacy,
particularly in the West.
And three, there has been a concerted effort
for many a years to paint all Arabs as terrorists.
So you should be able to look through these three truths
when you are viewing what is going on in Palestine and Israel.
You have that lens to see through.
And what I'm doing right here is showing you lines
that you should be reading between.
These are lines that you should be reading between.
Okay, critical thinking.
Thank you.